字幕翻译｜Hs 1 ao Han Huang
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
♪ Slipped through the cracks ♪
♪ Down to the floor ♪
♪ This is the reason ♪
♪ Honey, I'm calling for more ♪
♪ Shot into space ♪
♪ You're like a ghost in the dark ♪
海军陆战队员5 杀戮战场
♪ I don't think so ♪
♪ Baby, forevermore ♪
♪ I got the place ♪
♪ If you got the time ♪
♪ Set 'em up in the streets now ♪
♪ And knock 'em all down ♪
♪ Like an eraser ♪
♪ I'm rubbing hard ♪
♪ I play for keeps now, honey ♪
♪ I'm not getting out ♪
♪ Oh, I got the noose ♪
♪ If you got the heart ♪
♪ Taking you downtown, honey ♪
♪ Back to the start ♪
♪ Oh, I got the noose ♪
♪ You got the heart ♪
♪ Taking you downtown, honey ♪
♪ Oh, I got the noose ♪
♪ You got the heart ♪
♪ Taking you downtown, honey ♪
♪ Oh, I got the noose ♪
♪ You got the heart ♪
加把劲，兄弟
Keep it tight, man.
很快就要结束了
This will be over soon.
那不是他
Man, that's not him.
我欠你一百五十
I owe you 150 bucks.
所以我说的是追加一百五十
So, I'm talking about an extra $150.
我还能得到什么？
So what more can I get for that?
♪ Jokers driving wild ♪
[失踪军团]
♪ Some motherfucker ♪
大伙们
Guys.
怎么了，迪康？
What's up, Deacon?
怎么了？
What up?
嗯
Yeah.
你要去哪，宝贝？
WOWhere you going, baby?
喂
Yo.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hey!  - Hey!
他在这
There he is.
- 今晚不行  - 拜托…
- WONot tonight.  - Come on...
阿龙卓，怎么了，宝贝？
Alonzo. What's up, baby? Whoo!
- 嘿，菜鸟  - 怎么了，布？
- Hey, prospect.  - What's up, Boo?
- 罗锥勾在哪？ - 他在路上了
- Where's Rodrigo?  - He's on his way.
你没跟他在一起？
You ain't with him?
副会长在吧台那边有事
Vice President's business is at the bar.
来吧，宝贝
Come on, baby.
- 不对吗，小老弟？ - 他妈的没错
- Ain't that right, little brother?  - Damn right.
敬失踪军团
For the Legion.
好！
Yeah!
他在那，走吧
That's him. Let's go.
罗锥勾！
Rodrigo!
走！
Let's go. Let's go!
- 靠！ - 快！
- Shit!  - Come on! Come on!
- 那是啥？ - 我们走吧
- What was that?  - Let's go.
我们去追他们！
We're going after them!
把枪拿来！
Get the guns!
重整！
Re-stack!
我们会报仇的
We'll avenge this.
我跟你保证
I promise you.
- 什么情况？ - 一个大约三十的女人
- What do we got?  - One female about 30.
起重机正将砖块移到屋顶
Crane was lifting bricks onto the roof,
但有个白痴装太多导致起重机断裂
but some asshole overloaded it, one of the chains broke.
一半的砖块砸到她车上
Half the load landed on her car.
她还有意识，但卡在车里
She's conscious but trapped.
- 他就是那白痴？ - 对
- He the asshole?  - Yeah.
如果再有一条铁链断的话，全都会砸下来的
If another one of those chains goes, whole load'll come down.
现在进去太危险了
It's way too dangerous to go in right now.
我们会等到消防队来稳定局势
We're waiting on FD to secure it
再派人把她救出来
before anyone tries to get to her out.
- 他们在哪？ - 在路上，三分钟后到
- Where are they?  - En route, three minutes.
嘿，甜心，我们是救护队
Hey, sweetie. We're the ambulance crew.
我是卓，这是杰克，你的名字叫什么？
I'm Zoe, this is Jake. What's your name?
- 安娜  - 保持清醒
- Ana.  - Stay with us.
我们会尽快把你弄出来，好吗？
We're gonna have you out of there as soon as possible. Okay?
我的腿卡住了，我出不去，动不了
My legs are trapped, I can't get out, I can't move.
要把她弄出来
We gotta get her out of there.
在消防队来之前不能进去
No one goes in till the fire department gets here.
- 嘿，你有千斤顶吗？ - 杰克，你想都别想
- Hey, you got a car jack?  - Don't even think about it, Jake.
给我你的千斤顶，快
Give me your car jack. Come on, hurry up.
快
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
那些砖块随时都会掉下来的
Those bricks could fall down any second.
准备好，我要把她弄出来
Be ready when I get her out.
一旦我抓到她的腿，她血压就会开始降低
As soon as I free her legs, she'll start losing BP.
杰克！
Jake! Jake!
队长不会喜欢这样的
Captain ain't gonna like this.
靠
Shit.
嘿，安娜，你还好吗？救你出来好吗？
Hey, Ana. How you doing? What do you say we get you outta here?
只需要把这千斤顶放在这操纵杆之下
Just gonna put this car jack underneath the steering column.
这样可以释放一点在你腿上的压力，好吗？
It will release some pressure off your legs, okay?
- 安娜  - 哦，我的天
- Ana, Ana, Ana.  - Oh, my God.
嘿，不
Hey, no, no, no.
哦，我的天，我要死了
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die.
不，你没有
No, you're not. No, you're not. No, you're not.
看着我，一切都会没事的
Look at me. Look at me. Look at me, everything is okay.
一切都会没事的，我们快到那了
Everything is okay. Everything is okay. We're nearly there.
我们快到了
We're almost there.
一，二…
One, two...
- 杰克！ - …三
- Jake!  - ...three.
快
Come on.
快出来！
Get out of there!
我们接到她了！
We got her!
- 把她抬到担架上  - 她的动脉被切断了
- Get her on the gurney.  - Her artery is cut right through.
她休克了
She's in shock.
她已经流太多血了，她快不行了
She's lost too much blood already. We're losing her.
还没
Not yet. Not yet.
快，没脉搏
Come on. No pulse.
安娜
Ana. Ana.
- 大家给我们点空间  - 大家，散开
- Everybody give us some space.  - Folks, clear back for her
都散开
Clear back.
散开
Clear.
警官，交给你了
Sergeant, take over.
来
Come on.
杰克，我要宣告死亡时间了
Jake, I'm calling it.
还没
Not yet.
杰克，她走了
Jake, she's gone.
拜托，安娜
Come on, Ana!
拜托！
Come on!
你想跟我说你刚才在想什么吗？
You wanna tell me what's going through your head back there?
- 你自己也可能丧命  - 我得做点什么
- You could have been killed.  - I had to do something.
你该做的是确保…
What you have to do is make sure
每天下班都活着回家
you go home alive at the end of every shift.
我懂，但海军陆战队不一样
Look, I get it. It's different in the Marines.
我们永远不会抛弃同袍，等等
"We'll never leave a man behind," and all of that.
但外头还有好几千条命需要你救…
But there are thousands more out there who are gonna need your help...
但如果我死了我就救不了人了，对吗？
And I can't do that if I'm dead, right?
对
Right.
好
Yeah.
别急，今天只是你工作的第一天
Don't rush it. It's your first day on the job.
[欢迎来到大峰游乐场]
九一一，你怎么了？
911, what's your emergency?
我需要…帮助
I... I need help.
你知道关于我的一切吗？
So, you know everything about me?
我知道你所有的军队生涯
I know all about your military career.
海军陆战队的军士，在阿富汗待过两次
Sergeant in the Marines, two tours in Afghanistan,
在敌人面前展现无畏精神所得到的铜星牌
and a Bronze Star for displaying unwavering courage in the face of the enemy.
还有个短暂的私人保全经历，现在你在紧急救护队
And a very short engagement in private security, and now you're an EMT.
二七四队，大峰游乐场有状况
Medic 274, we've got a Code 3 at the Great Peaks Amusement Park.
收到，我们在路上
Ten-four, on our way.
男方说他心脏病发作，正在停车场里
Male says, he's having a heart attack. He's inside the parking lot.
- 多大？ - 我们只知道那些
- How old?  - That's all we got.
天知道他在那干嘛，游乐场夏天才开
The hell knows what he's doing down there, the park is closed until summer.
在一二〇街上右转，在那
Make a right on 120th, right there.
这什么鬼地方
Place is like a ghost town.
再几个礼拜
Give it a few weeks.
这地方就充斥着父母和小孩了
This place will be crawling with families and children.
在那，停车场
Over there. Parking lot's right there.
我们挤不进去
We're not gonna fit.
限高一百九十六公分，我们是两百五十四公分
It's a 6.6" restriction, and we're 8.4".
遣派，这里是二七四队
Dispatch, this is Medic 274.
二七四，请说
274, go ahead.
你确定他在停车场吗？
Are you sure that he's in the parking lot?
那是他说的
That's what he said.
我们挤不进去，所以我们步行进去
Okay. Well, we're not gonna fit, so we're proceeding on foot.
收到，二七四
Roger, 274.
- 恶作剧电话？ - 可能是
- Prank call?  - Most likely.
还是要看一眼
Still gotta check.
[门前禁止停车]
门坏了，有人真猴急
Gate's broken. Someone was in a hurry.
哈罗？紧急救护队！
Hello? EMS!
救护车！有人在吗？
Ambulance! Anybody here?
来，卡特，你会不会玩躲猫猫？
Come on, Carter. You any good at hide and seek?
[大峰游乐场入口指示]
哈罗
Hello.
有人在下面吗？
Anybody down here?
为何有心脏病还开来这里？
Why would someone drive down here with a heart attack?
一定是恶作剧
It had to be a prank.
- 我们走  - 等一下
- Let's go.  - Wait.
你听见了吗？
You hear that?
是台车
It's a car.
紧急救护队！你有叫救护车吗？
EMS! You call for an ambulance?
有人在卡车里吗？
Anybody in the truck?
弹孔
Bullet holes.
有人，在你那边
We got someone. Your side.
他死了
He's dead.
你觉得是他打九一一的吗？
You think he called 911?
他干嘛爬到乘客座？
Why would he climb in the passenger seat?
还有人在这里
There's someone else down here.
嘿，我们是紧急救护队，救护车
Hey. We're EMS. Ambulance.
喂，冷静，杰克
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, easy, easy, Jake.
你受伤了吗？是你打九一一的吗？
You hurt? You call 911?
放下，好吗？我们是来帮你的
Put that down! Okay? We're here to help you.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 柯尔
- What's your name?  - Cole.
想跟我们说发生什么事吗？
Do you wanna tell us what's going on?
我们因为有人心脏病被叫来，是你吗？
We got called to a heart attack. Is that you?
不要叫警察，拜托
No cops. Please. Please.
枪伤，腹部有大弹孔出口
GSW. Large exit wound in the abdomen.
腰部有小弹孔入口
Small entry hole in the lower back.
想跟我们说怎么了吗？
You wanna tell us what happened?
我们只是误闯禁区
Look, we were just rolling through the wrong hood,
结果一个帮派来伤害我们
and some gang came and cut us up.
你只是刚好握着枪自卫
You just happen to be holding a gun for your own protection.
什么都没做，对吗？
Didn't do anything, huh?
拜托，不要叫警察
Look, man, please, no cops.
我必须得报备
I'm gonna call this in.
啊！
Ahhh!
嘿
Hey.
我的兄弟，泰勒，在卡车里，他是不是…
My man Taylor, in the truck, is he...
他死了，我很抱歉
He's dead. I'm sorry.
我们在这下面没讯号
We don't have a signal down here.
我会从救护车里打电话
I'll call it in from the ambulance.
- 能把担架也扛下来吗？ - 你没事吧？
- Mind bringing the gurney down, too?  - You gonna be all right?
不是我第一次救帮派份子了
It's not my first time treating a gang-banger.
快去
Go. Go, go, go.
让我们确认一下这游乐场
Let's check the theme park.
阿龙卓，这里！
Alonzo, over there!
怎么有辆鬼救护车在这？
What the hell is an ambulance doing here?
- 游乐场关了  - 你觉得是为我们的人来的吗？
- The park is closed.  - You think it's for our guy?
我们看看
Let's find out.
关了
It's locked.
他他妈的在哪？
Where the fuck is he?
可能是任何人
This could be for anyone, man.
去看看
Hey, check it out.
是那辆攻击我们的卡车
That's from the truck that did the hit.
看
Look.
- 你要我打给文森吗？ - 别管文森
- You want me to call Vincent?  - Screw Vincent.
我来干
I'm running this.
- 我搞完打给他！ - 好
- I'll call him when it's done!  - All right, yo.
摩尔菲，你在楼梯掩护，迪康，去骑摩托车
Murphy, you cover the stairs. Deacon, mount up.
这狗娘养的今晚得死！
This son of a bitch dies tonight!
靠
Shit.
九一一，你怎么了？
911, what's your emergency?
- 杰克卡特，二七四队  - 说…
- Jake Carter, Medic 274.  - Go ahead...
哈罗？该死
Hello? Damn it!
去绕远路，我从这边去
Take the far ramp, I'll take this one.
我们得走了，现在
We gotta go! We gotta go, right now!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
一个摩托车帮派出现了，说他们要杀了他！
Some biker gang just turned up. Said they're gonna kill him!
- 干  - 你有叫遣派吗？
- Fuck.  - Did you inform dispatch?
没有，走不回救护车
Nah. Couldn't get to the ambulance.
你认识这些人吗？他们真的会来杀了你吗？
Do you know these people? Are they really gonna try and kill you?
对，我们该走了
Yeah. We should go.
好，我们走，帮我扶他
Okay, okay, let's move. Help me get him up.
- 好，他们是从哪来的？ - 从坡道来的
- Okay. Where are they coming from?  - Down the ramps.
- 好，我们走楼梯  - 不
- Okay. We'll take the stairs.  - No, no.
他们有人在那掩护了，把他带进卡车里，这是最好的方法了
They got 'em covered. Get him in the truck. It's our best chance.
深呼吸
Breathe. Breathe.
到车后，你可以吧？
In the bed. You got him?
他没事，喂！
I got him, I got him, I got him. Whoa, whoa!
进去吧，看着，好，放松
In you go. Watch it. Okay, easy.
- 压好你的伤口，柯尔？ - 好
- Put pressure on your wound, Cole?  - Yeah, yeah.
能压多大力就压多大力，好吗？
Put as much pressure on your wound as you can, okay?
门，看好
Door, watch it. Door.
- 喂！ - 只是以防万一
- Whoa!  - Just a precaution.
柯尔，看着我
Cole, look at me.
看着我，压好伤口，好吗？你很棒
Look at me. Pressure on the wound, okay? You're doing great.
靠
Shit.
低头！
Get your head down!
- 还好吗？ - 我还好
- Are you okay?  - I'm okay.
快把我们弄出这！
Just get us the hell out of here!
这卡车没用了，我们得找另个方法上去
This truck's wasted, we gotta find another way up.
一样的卡车，两个救护人员跟一个男的在后面
It's the same truck. Two medics and the guy in the back.
- 去电梯！ - 你自己来这边！
- Get to the elevator!  - Get yourself on this side!
快，我们走
Come on, let's go. Come on.
这没用！
It's not working!
电梯，上一层楼！
Stairwell, next level up!
走！
Go!
在他们之后进去，我断路，快走
Get in after 'em, I'll cut 'em off. Go, go, go.
你他妈的在干嘛？
The hell you doing?
这是他们出来的地方
This is where they came out, man.
两个救护人员和一个伤者都能跑过你？
Two paramedics and one wounded guy outran you?
快，检查全部的楼梯
Come on, man. Check the whole damn stairwell.
柱子后面，把他放下来
Behind the column. Behind the column. Set him down.
干
Fuck.
[楼梯间]　　[大峰游乐场此季不开放]
- 我们找到他了，有人来吗？ - 没有
- We found him. Anybody come up?  - Nope.
喂！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 他们没有在楼梯  - 也许他们从别的地方出去了
- They're not in the stairwell.  - Maybe they got out another way.
不，没有其他出口
No. There's no other exits.
这里也没有讯号
And there's no signal down there,
所以他们不会报警的
so they can't call the cops.
要我再找后援吗？
You want me to get some back up?
不，我们困住他们了
No. We've got 'em trapped.
嘿，我们没事了
Hey. Hey. We're okay now.
- 他们走了  - 好
- They're gone.  - Okay. Okay.
我没机会给你打麻药
I didn't get a chance to administer morphine
因为我们的急救箱在卡车里
because our kit's in the truck,
他的脉搏跟电动钻一样快，他要休克了
and his pulse is racing like a jackhammer. He's going into shock.
我们必须现在就把他送到创伤外科那
We need to get him to a trauma surgeon, right now.
为什么那些家伙找你？
Why are these guys after you?
我跟你说过了，因为我们误闯禁区，他们就朝我们开枪
I told you. We just rolled up in the wrong hood. They jumped us.
带着机关枪误闯禁区？
Rolled up in the wrong hood with a machine gun?
最好是
Sure.
你被卷入枪战，还拖我们下水来救你
You got hit in a gunfight and dragged us down here to save you.
警察才不会为了心脏病来，你杀了谁？
Cops don't show up for heart attacks. Who'd you kill?
- 有差吗？ - 有差吗？
- What does it matter?  - What does it matter?
我想知道那些家伙会有多想抓住我们
I want to know how far these guys will go to see this through.
你杀了谁？
Who did you kill?
他们的头头，罗锥勾
The head of this biker gang. Their leader. Rodrigo.
我是被逼的，我别无选择
Look, I was forced to, I had no choice.
连开枪的都不是我，我只负责开车
I didn't even pull the trigger. I just drove the truck.
他们哪都不会去，是吗？
They're not going anywhere, are they?
他妈的没错
Hell yeah.
[地下五楼]
[地下六楼]
主说：“要有光”
And the good Lord said, "Let there be light."
那手机呢？
And what about the cell phones?
如果他们来这，他们还是可以报警
Look, if they get up here, they can still call the cops.
往东十条街就有个讯号台
There's a cell tower 10 blocks east.
如果我们把那弄坏，我们就能完全把他们制伏了
If we knock that out, we have them on total lock-down.
- 动手吧  - 嘿，我的摩托车还在那边
- Do it.  - Hey, man, my bike's still down there.
骑她的
Well, take her bike.
说的对
Right on.
电梯还是不动，可能是用别的发电机
Elevator's still out. Must be on a different power supply.
好，我们从楼梯走去公园
Okay. We can take the stairs and make it to the park.
我们不可能绕过他们的，而且还有他在
We'll never get past them, especially carrying him.
喂，救护人员！
Yo, paramedics!
我们不要再玩躲猫猫了
We ain't playing no more hide and seek.
我们也不会走的
And we ain't leaving neither.
除非你们把那小丑给我们
Not till you give me that clown
你们一定是躲在下面！
you've got hiding down there!
你们还有三分钟可以交出他
You have three minutes to hand him over,
不然我们就要来杀了你
or we're coming down to kill you.
你自己选吧
Your choice.
不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- 嘿  - 怎么会这样，这太疯狂了
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey.  - This can't be happening. This is crazy.
- 我会想办法的  - 想什么办法？
- I'll work this out.  - Work what out?
他已经失血至少一小时了
Look, he's been hemorrhaging blood for at least an hour.
他可能都已经没了百分之十的血
He's lost probably 10% already.
- 我可以让他稳定  - 用什么？
- I can stabilize him.  - With what?
我们没有工具
Look, we don't have the equipment.
他需要输血
He needs a blood transfusion.
卡特，我们能做的都做了
Carter, there's nothing more that we can do.
我们不会交出他的
We're not handing him over.
我能听到你说话
You know, I can hear you.
我们上次要求遣派是何时？
When did we last contact dispatch?
- 凌晨一点五十分  - 那就是四十分钟前
- 1:50 AM.  - So that's 40 minutes ago.
若我们二十分钟内不回应
If we don't respond in the next 20 minutes,
他们就会派警车到我们上次的地点，对吗？
they'll send a cop car to our last location, right?
- 规矩是那样  - 好
- That's protocol.  - Okay.
所以我们找个地方躲起来，直到他们来到这
So we find a place to hide, and hole up till they get here.
那个管理门，我们躲在那没人会看见
That maintenance door, we'll be out of sight in there.
我们需要紧急救护箱来稳定他
We need our kit to stabilize him,
不然他会没命的
or he's not gonna make it.
我去卡车那拿箱子，你把他带到门那
I'll get the kit from the truck, you get him to the door.
如果我们这样做，警察会来的
Look, if we do this, it's gonna be cops coming.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
我只想再见我女儿一面
I just wanna see my baby girl again.
好，我们开始吧
Okay. Let's do this.
好，我们走！对，我来照顾他，走
Okay. Let's go. Yeah. Yeah. I got him. I got him. Let's go.
别停
Don't stop.
二七四队，进来
Medic 274, come in.
拜托，大伙们，状况如何？
Come on, guys. What's the status of that Code 3?
快接无线电，卓
Pick up the radio, Zoe, or it's your ass
不然我就要报警了
if I have to haul in a black-and-white.
靠
Shit.
我们必须找到他们，现在，看楼梯！上！
We need to find 'em, right now! Check the stairs! Go!
阿龙卓
Alonzo.
去下面把他们赶出来
Get down there and flush them out.
别动
Don't move!
把手举起来
Show me your hands.
我只是救护人员，不用这样
I'm just a medic.
开启，能量选择▲充电▲电击
You don't have to do this.
我说，把手举起来！
I said, show me your hands!
别那样，别…
Don't do it. Don't...
我们快到了
We're nearly there. Nearly there.
好
Okay.
- 去柱子后面  - 干
- Behind the pillar.  - Behind the pillar. Fuck.
他回来了
He's coming back around.
柯尔…
Cole...
你可以自己走到门吗？
Can you make it to the door by yourself?
可以
Yeah. Yeah.
- 我来让他们分心  - 不，等一下
- I'll create a diversion.  - No. Wait.
杰克！杰克，救命！
Jake! Jake, help!
杰克！
Jake! Jake!
- 卓在哪？ - 他们抓到她了
- Where's Zoe?  - They got her.
靠
Shit.
嘿，有什么可以止痛的吗？
Hey, hey, hey, hey. You think I could get something for the pain?
拜托
Please. Please, man.
二七四队，重复，你现在情况如何？
274, again, what's your status?
时机刚好，给我起来
Well, you're just in time. Get off your ass.
二七四队，立刻回复
274, report immediately.
跟他们说你没事
Open it up and tell them you're okay.
我没钥匙
I don't have the key.
拜托，大伙们，我需要你们回答
Come on, you guys. I need you to check in.
告诉他们你没事
Tell them you're okay.
卓，我已经受不了了
Zoe, I'm getting really tired of this.
这值得拼命吗？
Is it worth dying for?
- 告诉他们  - 够了
- Tell them.  - That's it.
我要派警车了
I'm sending in a black and white.
二七四队回覆
Medic 274 responding.
终于，威廉斯
Well, about time, Williams.
你跑去哪了？需要支援吗？
Where have you been? Do you need assistance?
跟他们说没事
Tell them it was nothing.
说只是个恶作剧，没什么好汇报的
It was just a prank. Nothing to report.
收到，二七四队，留线待命，完毕
Copy, 274. Stay on the air in the future. Out.
没人会来救你了
No one's coming to save your ass now.
你确定吗？
Are you sure about that?
闭嘴！
Shut up!
我的伙伴，他不是一般的救护人员
My partner, he's not just some kind of paramedic.
他以前还是海军陆战队，受训过的杀手
He's an ex-Marine, a trained killer.
他会在放弃那孩子之前
And he'll send every last one of you guys
先把你们一个个送进地狱
to hell before he deserts that kid.
- 靠，放松  - 你到底想不想要吗啡？
- Ah! Shit. Take it easy.  - You want morphine, or not?
你叫什么名字？
What's your name, man?
卡特，杰克卡特
Carter. Jake Carter.
我们需要换一下这个
We need to change this.
我很抱歉我把你们叫来
Look, I'm sorry I called you down here.
我为这一切道歉
Sorry any of this happened.
把这压好
Put pressure here.
我只是在保护我的女儿
I was just protecting my daughter.
我想要她好好长大
I wanted her to grow up safe.
现在看来我也活不了多久了
Now it looks like I'm not even gonna be around.
你会活的
You'll be around.
振作点
Hold it together.
我的宝贝五岁了
My baby girl's five now.
我在蹲时每天都拿着这个
I had this with me every day when I was on the inside.
你坐过牢？
You were in prison?
我在人生中做过一些错事
Look, man, I've done some dumb things in my life,
但我不是坏人
but I ain't a bad person.
今晚以前我从没拿过枪
I never even held a gun before tonight.
现在别想那个了，想想这个
Don't think about that now. Think about this.
为这个活着
Live for this.
现在我要去看看我伙伴了
Now, I gotta go see about my partner.
嘿，锅盖头
Hey, jarhead.
你在听吗？
You listening?
你朋友在我们手上，她有话要跟你说
We got your girl, and she's got something she has to tell you.
跟他说，他必须知道你还活着
Tell him. He has to know you're still alive.
他们让我撤遣派，杰克，没人要来了
They made me reply to dispatch, Jake. No one's coming.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你听到了吗？
You hear that?
风水轮流转，要换我们占上风了
The odds are stacked, and we've got the winning hand.
问题是，谁的命你比较在乎？
The only question is, which life do you value most?
她的？还是你在下面保护的那斓货？
Hers? Or that cockroach you got down there with you?
别把我交出去，拜托
Don't give me in, man, please.
该做出选择了，混帐！
Time to make a choice, asshole!
拜托，锅盖头
Come on, jarhead.
那孤僻鬼杀了我们的人
That lone wolf killed one of our own.
正义是我们的！以牙还牙！
We deserve justice! Blood for blood!
孤僻鬼？
Lone wolf?
我数到三
I'm gonna count to three.
- 一！ - 他们认识你吗？
- One!  - Do they know you?
- 什么？ - 他们认得你吗？
- What?  - Do they know your face?
- 我不知道  - 二
- I don't know.  - Two.
他们看过你吗？他们有看过你吗？
Did they see you? Did they actually see you?
没有，只有会长
No. No, just the president.
三
Three.
停！别开枪！
Stop! Don't shoot!
别杀她！我同意！
Don't kill her! I'll do it!
- 我会交换  - 不
- I'll make the trade.  - No.
我在楼下！快来找他！
I'm on the bottom level! Come and get him!
- 我需要你的外套  - 什么？
- I need your jacket.  - What?
- 你在干嘛？ - 他们以为只有一个人
- What are you doing?  - They think it's one guy.
快骑上摩托车，给我你的手
Get your ass on the bike. Give me your hands.
你知道要做什么
You know what to do.
文森，我是阿龙卓
Vincent, it's Alonzo.
我们在游乐场的地下车库
We're at the underground garage at the amusement park.
完事了
Job's done.
他死了！
He's dead!
是你吗，锅盖头？
That you, jarhead?
现身
Show yourself.
你有你想要的了
You got what you wanted.
现在放开我的伙伴后走吧
Now let my partner go, and leave.
对
Yeah.
要不然我杀了你的婊子伙伴，把你剁了喂狗如何？
How about I blast your bitch partner, carve you up for my dogs?
然后我再走
And then I'll leave.
听见了吗？
Hear that?
这是一把直径点三五七的枪弄出来的声音
That's the first noise a .357 makes.
想在这待会儿吗？
Wanna hang around for the second?
鬼扯
Bullshit.
干！他他妈的从哪拿来的？
Fuck! Where the hell did he get that?
从你朋友那
From your friend.
在我将刀插进她肚子后
After I stuck a knife in her gut.
我刚说什么了？
What did I say?
你这混帐！
You son of a bitch!
迪康，你会得到正义的
Deacon. You will get justice.
你想要正义？
You want justice?
他偷袭了我们
He flanked us.
在这
There it is.
正义，在你脚边
Justice. At your feet.
上面有刺青吗？
There ain't no ink on that body?
那才不是摩托车帮的
That ain't no biker.
他什么时候死的？
When did he die?
二十分钟前
Twenty minutes ago.
我做了一切我能做的
I did all I could.
为什么你之前不交出他
Why didn't you give him up before?
因为我觉得就算我交出他，你也不会放了我伙伴
'Cause I didn't think you'd let my partner go even if I did.
谁说我现在就会？
Who's to say I will now?
值得一试
Me being a good shot.
他他妈的在哪？
Where the fuck is he?
好了，锅盖头
All right, jarhead.
换你了
Your round.
把那鬼东西照起来
Photograph that piece of shit.
想把我从这堆弄出来吗？
Wanna help me get out of these?
不！
No!
你真的以为我们就会这样离开吗，锅盖头？
You really think we'll just walk away, jarhead?
你不知道你闯了什么祸
You don't know what you just started.
都被困住了还敢讲大话
Big words for a cornered rat.
文森随时都会到，我们找到我们来找的那家伙了
Vince will be here soon. We got the guy we came here for.
- 锅盖头怎办？ - 我们到楼上后解决他
- What about the jarhead?  - We'll cut him off at the top.
走吧
Let's go.
你说你这边都完事了？
You said you were done here?
结束了
We are done. It's over.
今天对我们帮派来说真糟
It's a dark day for our club.
但正义与我们同在，我恭喜你
But justice has been dealt. I congratulate you.
我们抓到那混帐了
We got that son of a bitch.
他死了
He's dead.
- 那另一个呢？ - 什么另一个
- What about the other one?  - What other one?
- 有两个家伙来闹事  - 什么？
- There were two guys who did the hit.  - What?
不，就一个人，我看见他了
No, it was a lone wolf, I saw him.
- 什么时候？ - 我们到这的时候
- When?  - When we got here.
紧急救护队来试着把他救出去
The EMTs tried to bust him out with the pickup.
后头还有个家伙受伤
There was one wounded guy in the back.
我看了警卫室监视器了，阿龙卓！
I watched the security tapes, Alonzo!
卡车里有两个人，两个！
There were two guys in that truck. Two!
一个开车，一个开枪，你蠢吗？
A driver and a shooter. Are you stupid?
意思就是有一个还在外头！
That means one of them bastards is still out there!
嗯
Huh.
没子弹了吧？
Out of bullets, huh?
我还有很多子弹
I got lots of bullets.
斧头兵降临
The axeman cometh.
拜托
Oh, please.
- 谢谢你来帮忙  - 谢谢你给我吗啡
- Thanks for the help.  - Thanks for the morphine.
嘿，救护人员
Hey, paramedic!
我们知道那混球不是自己一个人在下面！
We know that motherfucker wasn't alone down there!
叫支援
Call for backup.
我有枪，子弹，和无线电
All right? I want guns, ammo, and radios.
我会把这混帐赶出来的
I'll flush this bastard out.
走！
Go on!
有人在骗我们他有很多子弹，是吗？
Someone was lying about having lots of ammo, weren't they?
柯尔
Cole.
柯尔，嘿，柯尔
Cole. Hey. Cole.
你还醒着吗？
You still with me?
嗯
Yeah.
你的伙伴在哪？
Where's your partner?
她死了，他们杀了她
She's dead. They killed her.
干
Fuck.
嘿！
Hey!
救护人员先生！
Mr. Paramedic man!
你不认识我
You don't know me,
但看看，我一支独秀！
but see here, I run this show!
我有更多人和枪在路上
I got more men and more guns coming.
就算我们把这整个停车场翻遍
And we're gonna sweep every inch
也要找到你
of this place until we find you.
我会找到你
And I will find you!
我没用了，兄弟，你已经尽你所能了
Look, I'm wasted, man, you've done all you can.
就走吧
Just go.
你自己一个人更有机会从这出去
You got a better chance of making it out of here alone.
这些家伙杀了我同伴
These guys killed my partner.
我们同病相怜，来吧
We're in this together now. Come on.
我们要让电梯动起来，这样才能出去
We're gonna get the elevator working. Get us the hell out.
我们今晚不会死在这的
We're not dying here tonight.
楼下，早知道了
Bottom floor. Figures.
来吧
Come on.
柯尔，来
Cole. Cole. Cole. Come on, man.
要帮你输点血
Gotta get some blood into you.
我们走！
Let's go!
我找到他了
I got him.
我们走
Let's go.
- 我们可以的  - 我们可以替罗锥勾还个公道！
- We can do this.  - We can. Do it for Rodrigo.
在这，卸在这吧
Over here, unload it here.
我知道
I got it.
- 我们在哪？ - 在电梯里
- Where are we?  - In the elevator.
你刚刚心膊要停止了
You were going into cardiac arrest.
这是战斗输血，我是0型血，没事的
It's combat transfusion. I'm O positive. It's safe.
战斗什么？
Combat what?
在海陆是基本训练
It's standard practice in the Marines.
- 你是海军陆战队的？ - 是
- You're a Marine?  - Yes, sir.
难怪你这么勇猛
No wonder you're such a badass.
天哪
Oh, God.
噢！
Oh.
你干嘛这样？
Why did you do all this?
这是笔债
It was a debt.
我在牢里时，有个家伙给我和泰勒庇护
When I was in jail, some guy offered me and my buddy Taylor protection.
当我们出来时，我们说我们欠他的
When we got out, said we owed him.
他让你替他杀人？
He told you to kill somebody for him?
对，跟他曾有不合的摩托车帮头头
Yeah, head of some biker gang he had beef with.
我们不要，但他伤害了泰勒的兄弟
We said no, but then he came after Taylor's brother,
至今未醒
put him in a coma.
他说我的女儿就是下一个，天哪
He told me my baby girl was next. God.
我别无选择，我必须这样
I had no choice, I had to do it.
我向罗锥勾发过誓
I made a promise to Rodrigo
我会替他报仇
that I'd avenge his death.
而作为你们的新头头
And as your new leader,
我会把这当作我第一个政绩
I am making this my first order of business.
敬失踪军团！
For the Legion!
好，这样应该就行了
Okay, that's gonna have to do.
啊！
Ow!
- 天哪  - 我会让这东西动的
- God.  - I'm gonna get this thing working.
- 我们开始吧  - 我们走
- Let's do it.  - Let's go.
- 来  - 为了罗锥勾
- Come on.  - For Rodrigo.
你知道你在干嘛吗？
Do you know what you're doing?
你爬楼梯，我们走坡道
You take the stairs. We'll take the ramps.
你知道怎么给车起火吗？
You know how to hot-wire a car?
干嘛，就因为我蹲过，我就要知道怎么帮车起火吗？
What, just because I've been to jail, I know how to hot-wire a car?
好，我知道，但那不一样
Okay, I do, but it's not the same.
这是我们唯一的机会，快跟我说要怎么做
It's our only chance. Talk me through it quick.
要拿出黄线，但别剪
You wanna take out the yellow wire, but don't cut it.
把它绑到白线上
Tie it to the white one.
黄线？没有黄线啊
Yellow? There is, there is no yellow.
来吧，大伙们，该赢得那些了
Come on, boys. Time to earn those patches.
让我们开干吧
Let's do it.
所以你要把那条电线绑到…
So you wanna take the wire and tie it to the...
- 有绿线  - 对，绿线，绑到绿线
- There's a green.  - Yeah, the green. Tie it to the green.
哇喔
Whoa!
他们在电梯里
They're in the elevator.
不
No.
我想知道是哪个帮派，还有谁盼咐攻击的
I wanna find out which gang they're from, and who ordered the hit.
是他们，他们在外面
It's them, man. They're outside.
打开
Get it open.
快点
Come on.
- 混帐  - 去开开看楼上的门
- Son of a bitch.  - Try the door a level above.
靠
Shit.
嘿，别离开我
Hey, don't leave me, man.
靠
Oh, shit.
快，走
Come on, come on. Go.
刹车一直让我们前进不了
Brakes are holding us down.
我们把它们射掉，这样就可以到上面了
We shoot 'em off, we go all the way to the top.
靠
Oh, shit.
给我枪
Give me the shotgun.
快，柯尔，枪给我
Come on, Cole. Give me the shotgun.
伸手
Reach.
我要来找你了
I'm coming to get you.
他们要从上面过来了，柯尔，给我枪
They're coming through the top. Give me the gun, Cole.
打开
Open up. Open up.
好
All right.
不
No.
他们在电梯里，要去游乐场里了
They're in the elevator and they're heading to the park.
我们走
Let's go.
上去吗？
Going up?
我们走
Let's go.
快！快！
Come on. Come on.
快走！
Move!
去看看
Check it.
嘿
Hey.
我们走
Let's go.
我们要去侧门
We're heading to the side entrance.
去上面看
Check it out up there.
好
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[鬼屋]
[出口]
你看到他就立刻开枪
You see him, you shoot on sight,
听到没？
you hear me?
我们要他活着
We need him alive.
他今晚得死！
He dies tonight!
听从命令！
Do what you're told!
我必须知道为什么
I need to know why.
听话，阿龙卓，我才是发号施令的人
Get in line, Alonzo. I'm the one giving orders.
靠
Shit.
干他妈的鬼屋
Fucking haunted houses!
抓到你了
Got you.
刚尼尔？锅盖头不在这，是个诱饵，他会去你那
Gunner? The jarhead's not here, it's a decoy. He's gotta be where you are.
刚尼尔，你听见了吗？
Gunner, are you hearing me?
回我！
Respond!
你有听到我说的吗？
Did you hear what I said?
刚尼尔，回电！
Gunner, pick up.
你有听到我说的吗？
Did you hear what I said?
回话
Come in.
刚尼尔，快接
Gunner. Pick up.
我是刚尼尔
Yeah. This is Gunner.
我死了，锅盖头杀了我
I'm dead. Jarhead just killed me.
他把所有的枪都拿走了
He's taken all my guns.
你冷血的杀了我的同伴，所以我们来个交易
You killed my partner in cold blood. So here's the deal.
很简单
Gonna make it real simple for you.
我已经徒手杀了你们帮里四个人
I've already taken down four of your guys with my bare hands.
我现在又有枪火
Now, I got some firepower.
不像你们这群白痴，我真的知道怎么用枪
And unlike you idiots, I actually know how to use it.
所以现在离开
So either walk away now,
不然就等死
or join your friends.
你自己选吧
Choice is yours.
- 你还好吗？ - 我还好
- You okay?  - Hanging in there.
海陆，你死定了
Marine, get fucked.
他们听起来不像想谈判
Doesn't sound like they wanna negotiate.
我来让他们分心
I'm gonna create a diversion.
让他们跑到游乐场另一头
Draw them to the other side of the park.
等你听到枪响
Wait till you hear gunfire,
就赶快到出口，知道吗？
then make a break for the exit. Got it?
知道
Got it.
快
Come on. Ahhh!
- 祝好运  - 你也是
- Good luck.  - You, too.
[抱歉 此座不开放]
[海盗船]
这他妈的是什么？
What the fuck is this?
他在这附近
He's here somewhere.
他们在哪？
Where they at?
下去！
Get down!
- 他在哪？ - 掩护我！
- Where is he?  - Cover me!
那里，在那！
There! Right there!
[娱乐中心]
在那
There.
留意锅盖头，这小子他妈的在哪？
Got eyes on the jarhead. But where the fuck is the kid?
在那！
There!
来吧！
Come on!
我们让他跑了
We got him running.
- 去右侧切断他去路  - 好
- Take the right flank, cut him off.  - All right.
你跟我来！
You, with me!
你完蛋了，混帐！
You're finished, asshole!
告诉我们他在哪！
Tell us where he is!
来吧，现在！
Come on, now!
该是时候结束一切了！把他交出来！
It's time to end this! Hand him over!
来抓他！
Come get him!
我抓到他了
I got him, man.
他他妈的玩完了
He's fucking done.
我们要来抓的混帐在哪？
Where's the son of a bitch we came for?
我抓到了，活的
I got him. Alive.
我们现在搞清楚是谁送你来的
Now we find out who sent you.
没刺青，就跟另一个家伙一样
No ink, just like that other guy.
啊！
Ah!
你是谁？
Who are you?
- 哪个帮派来的？ - 我没有帮派
- What gang are you from?  - I am not from any gang.
那你干嘛干这种活？
Then why you'd do it?
我别无选择，他们逼我的
I had no choice. I was forced to.
谁逼你的？
By who?
杀了那条狗
Put that dog down.
他！就是他！
Him! It was him.
- 他让我干的  - 滚到一边，阿龙卓
- He made me do it.  - Step aside, Alonzo.
- 他在说什么？ - 他在说谎！滚到一边
- What's he talking about?  - He's lying! Step aside.
- 他在说什么？ - 我他妈的射你！
- What's he talking about?  - I'll fucking shoot you!
我没在说谎！
I am not lying!
我们之前一起在圣昆汀州立监狱，E区
We were in San Quentin together, E block.
我一出狱他就逼我这样做，他威胁了我的家人
He forced me to do it once I got out. He threatened my family.
你之前就在E区
You were in E block.
暗杀是你计划的？
You ordered the hit?
- 是不是你计划的？ - 我必须那样！
- Did you order a hit?  - I had to!
你必须那样？
You had to?
为什么？
Why?
罗锥勾很懦弱
Rodrigo was weak.
跟其他帮派结党营私
Making alliances with other gangs.
军团团员不分享，我们抢！
Legionnaires don't share, we take!
他在扼杀我们的帮派！
He was killing this club!
你们要是没看见就是他妈的瞎了
And y'all are fucking blind if you don't see it!
你要管管吗，阿龙卓？
Are you gonna take charge, Alonzo?
你他妈的垃圾叛徒！
You traitor piece of shit!
干！
Fuck!
混帐，我杀了你们每个人
Son of a bitch, I'll fucking kill every one of you!
不！
No!
他是我的血亲，放了他
He's my blood. Leave him.
我为了你这么做，我为了我们！
I did this for you, I did it for us!
大哥，这是为了失踪军团
This is for the Legion, big brother.
哦，天哪，不！
Oh, God, no! No!
换你了
You're next.
天，该死！
Oh, God! Damn!
感觉如何？
How's that feel, huh?
嗯？
Huh?
- 让他血流干！ - 不
- Let him bleed out!  - No.
不，把汽油拿来
No. Get that gasoline.
什么？不
What? No. No.
- 没错  - 不
- Yeah.  - No, no, no, no.
今晚
Tonight,
我们要来点小烤肉派对
we're gonna have ourselves a little barbecue, huh?
听着，我有个女儿，好吗？
Listen, man, I have a daughter. Okay?
我有个小女儿
Oh. I got a little girl.
那是警察吗？
Is that cops?
是他
It's him.
滚开！
Move!
来吧！滚开！
Come on! Move your ass!
啊！
Argh!
该死！
God damn!
他是我的
He's mine, man. He's mine.
快走
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
去你的！
Fuck you!
嘿，卡特，可以让海陆帮个忙吗？
Yo, Carter, I could really use some Marine shit.
用绳索谄死他
Use the strap, choke him out!
卡特
Carter.
卡特，转轮子
Carter, turn the wheel.
你还好吗？
You okay?
拜托，给我个讯号
Come on, give me a signal.
干
Oh, fuck.
- 现在怎么办？ - 他要来了
- Now what?  - He's coming, he's coming.
救护车坏了，抓好
Ambulance is dead. Grab on to something.
高处没人，我们走，来
Come on. High ground, it's clear. Let's go, come on.
来，就是这样
Come on. That's it.
没讯号
No signal.
靠
Oh, shit.
我们必须继续前进
We gotta keep moving, come on.
快来
Come on.
靠，快来
Shit. Come on, come on, come on.
你要他吗？
You want him?
得先经过我
You'll have to go through me.
靠
Shit.
快，我们快走，快来
Come on, here we go, we gotta move. Come on. Come on!
继续走
Keep going.
快
Come on.
我们有讯号了
We got a signal. We got a signal.
杰克卡特，二七四队
Jake Carter, Medic 274.
我有个伤患，枪伤，大失血
I've got a wounded man, GSW, severe hemorrhaging.
立即遣派医疗和警方援护
Request immediate medical assistance and police backup.
我们在施工区
We're at the construction site,
圣卡洛斯大道的西边
west of San Carlos Boulevard...
上屋顶，去！
Get to the roof. Go!
我要杀了那小子，锅盖头
I'm gonna kill that kid, jarhead.
嘿，死人
Hey, dead man!
嘿，你，死人
Yeah, you, dead man.
你听见了吗？
You hear me?
我要来找你了
I'm coming for you.
你再跑也没用了
There ain't no sense in running no more.
报应的时候到了，混帐
It's the hour of reckoning, you son of a bitch.
别动
Stop.
警察要来了
The cops are coming.
是吗？那就让他们看着
Yeah? Well, let's give them a show.
你准备好飞了吗？
You ready to fly?
首先，你跳下这楝楼
First, you go off this building,
然后我就去找你家人
then I'm gonna come find your family.
我会把他们锁在屋里
I'm gonna lock them in a house,
一把火把他们烧成灰！
and then I'm gonna burn it to the ground!
听见了吗？
Do you hear me?
干！
Fuck!
你的大腿动脉爆裂了
Your femoral artery is ruptured.
必须得有个止血带，不然你再几分钟就会流血身亡的
You need a tourniquet, or you're gonna bleed to death in minutes.
快帮我
Yeah. Well, do it.
快啊！
Do it! Come on!
你杀了我同伴
You murdered my partner.
不
No, no. No, no, no.
不，别走
No, no, no. Don't go. No, no, no.
你是个救护人员，那是你的工作
You're a paramedic. It's your job.
做好你的工作
Do what's right.
啊！
Ahhh!
我会像杀了你婊子同伴一样杀了你
I'm gonna kill you like I killed your bitch partner.
天杀的
Oh, God damn.
这样才像海陆
Now, that's some Marine shit.
谢了，说的对
Thanks for your statement. Yeah, thanks.
可以给我点时间吗？
Can you give me a minute?
他会没事吧？
He gonna be all right?
你输的血应该救了他的命
That transfusion you did probably saved his life.
他会没事的
He'll be fine.
你之前掉了这个，我想你会想要留着的
You dropped this earlier. I didn't think you'd wanna leave it behind.
我得告诉警方所有事
I'm gonna have to tell the cops everything.
- 你知道那件事？ - 嗯，我猜到了
- You know that?  - Yeah, I figured.
意思就是你得回去蹲了
Means you're going back to jail.
至少我能看见我女儿长大
At least I get to see my baby girl grow up.
- 嘿，卡特  - 嗯？
- Hey, Carter.  - Yeah?
谢谢你救我的命
Thanks for keeping me alive.
那是我的职责
It's my job.
♪ Go tell everyone you know ♪
♪ There's a new voice ♪ ♪ that they need to hear ♪
♪ They'll be standing in them lines ♪
♪ Wanting me to sign a souvenir ♪
♪ You want the best Forget the rest ♪
♪ What you get is what you get with me ♪
♪ 'Cause if I'm walking by your side ♪
♪ Well, there's no place else ♪ ♪ you need to be ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ I throw two on the fire ♪
♪ Cut through all the wires ♪
♪ What I do You have to stop and admire ♪
♪ You better know your wish ♪
♪ I ain't playing for kicks ♪
♪ There's only one space ♪ ♪ at the top And I'm the one ♪
♪ And I'll always be the one ♪
♪ Always be the one ♪
♪ Well, any time, any place ♪
♪ There ain't nothing ♪ ♪ that I have to prove ♪
♪ And if you lock me in a cage ♪
♪ I'll bust out with my Houdini moves ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ I throw two on the fire ♪
♪ Cut through all the wires ♪
♪ What I do You have to stop and admire ♪
♪ You better know your wish ♪
♪ I ain't playing for kicks ♪
♪ There's only one space ♪ ♪ at the top And I'm the one ♪
♪ And I'll always be the one ♪
♪ Always be the one ♪
♪ I throw two on the fire ♪
♪ Cut through all the wires ♪
♪ What I do You have to stop and admire ♪
♪ You better know your wish ♪
♪ I ain't playing for kicks ♪
♪ There's only one space ♪ ♪ at the top And I'm the one ♪
♪ And I'll always be the one ♪
♪ Always be the one ♪